A Guide to the Papers of Henry Heth, 1765-1800
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Letter from E. V. Childe to C. H. Randolph 1837 (Box 16)
- Letter from Anne R. Lee to Charles Randolph 1837 (Box 16)
- Accounts and receipts for 1837 1837 (Box 16)
- Letter from T. Biddle to John B. Chapman 1838 Apr 29 (Box 16)
- Letter from A. Wooldridge to John Heth 1838 Jul 20 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. A. Kendall to John Heth 1838 Aug 17 (Box 16)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Charles H. Randolph 1838 Oct 29 (Box 16)
- Permission for Charles Randolph to practice medicine at Philadelphia Hospital 1838 Nov 1 (Box 16)
- Tickets to a series of lectures 1838-1839 (Box 16)
- Accounts and receipts for 1838 1838 (Box 16)
- Letter from James M. Hains to Beverly Randolph 1839 Mar 4 (Box 16)
- Letter from Peter Cook to Walter H. Taylor 1839 Mar 16 (Box 16)
- Letter from T. R. Price to W. H. Taylor & Co. 1839 Mar 16 (Box 16)
- Letter from William Allen to W. H. Taylor & Co. 1839 Mar 18 (Box 16)
- Letter from W. B. Porter to George W. H. 1839 Apr 5 (Box 16)
- Law suit-Etna Coal Co. vs. Beverly Randolph 1839 Jun 3 (Box 16)
- John Clarke's certificate 1839 Jun 8 (Box 16)
- Letter from N. R. McKenna to Beverly Randolph 1839 Jun 16 (Box 16)
- Letter from M. M. Robinson to Charles Randolph 1839 Sep 17 (Box 16)
- Letter from A. L. Ogden to John Heth 1839 Sep 20 (Box 16)
- Letter from A. L. Ogden to Henry [?] 1839 Sep 20 (Box 16)
- Certificate of William H. Rogers 1839 Nov 17 (Box 16)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to John Heth 1839 Dec 25 (Box 16)
- Letter from Charles Cunningham to Harry Heth 1839 Dec 31 (Box 16)
- Memorandum on horse named Bizzarre 183[?] (Box 16)
- Accounts and receipts for 1839 1839 (Box 16)
- Invitation to John Heth from Rowand Ronald 1840 (Box 16)
- Letter from Henry Hemlocke to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Richard Roberts to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to [John Heth] [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from W. F. Cunningham to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from W. F. Cunningham to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Tyrone Power to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Abraham Warwick to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Benjamin Rush to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Tyrone Power to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from S. C. Stevenson to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Benjamin Rush to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Tyrone Power to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from W. F. Cunningham to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from A. S. to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Benjamin Rush to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Thomas White to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from J. S. Slade to [John Heth] [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from C. Scarisbrick to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Scarisbrick to John Heth [1840] (Box 16)
- Letter from Rowand Ronald to John Heth 1840 Jan 7 (Box 16)
- Letter from Maria L. Ronald to John Heth 1840 Jan 18 (Box 16)
- Letter from Emma s. Reighty to John Heth 1840 Jan 28 (Box 16)
- Letter from Charles Cunningham to Harry Heth 1840 Feb 13 (Box 16)
- Letter from A. Stevenson to John Heth 1840 Mar 3 (Box 16)
- Letter from Benjamin Rush to John Heth 1840 Mar 13 (Box 16)
- Letter from Thomas Wood to [John Heth] 1840 Mar 21 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. T. Slade to [John Heth] 1840 Apr 9 (Box 16)
- Letter from Rowand Randolph to John Heth 1840 Apr 14 (Box 16)
- Letter from J. T. Slade to [John Heth] [1840] Apr 15 (Box 16)
- Letter from Charles Cunningham to [John Heth] [1840] Apr 22 (Box 17)
- Letter from R. S. Baker to John Heth [1840] Apr 28 (Box 17)
- Letter from J. T. Slade to John Heth 1840 Apr 30 (Box 17)
- Letter from J. T. Slade to John Heth 1840 Apr 30 (Box 17)
- Letter from John J. Fanish to John Heth 1840 May 27 (Box 17)
- Letter from John J. Fanish to John Heth 1840 Jun 12 (Box 17)
- Letter from Samuel Amory to John Heth 1840 Aug 31 (Box 17)
- Letter from Mr. Barclay to John Heth 1840 Sep 6 (Box 17)
- Letter from Samuel Amory to John Heth 1840 Sep 8 (Box 17)
- Letter from James Lyons to John Heth 1840 Oct 17 (Box 17)
- Letter from John M. Harvey to John Heth 1840 Dec 18 (Box 17)
- Letter from B. W. Leigh to Harry Heth 1841 Jan 27 (Box 17)
- Accounts and receipts for 1840 1840 (Box 17)
- Accounts and receipts n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from John Banks to Henry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- J. Reynold's memo n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Vincent Gray to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Memorandum n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from John B. Armistead to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Pedigree of Amazone n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Mr. Morris to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Omis Paine to [?] n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from J. A. Grant to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Memorandum n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from [?] to Henry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from W. B. Banister to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from J. Heth to Henry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Charles B. Peterson to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Map n.d. (Box 17)
- Memorandum re steam engine n.d. (Box 17)
- Memorandum re furnace n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Benjamin W. Finney to John Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Pictures n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Lavinia Randolph n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Sally Stewart to Lavinia R. Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from N. G. to Lavinia R. Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from A. W. Harrison to Harry Heth [?] Nov 25 (Box 17)
- Schedule of coal lands owned by Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Subscriptions for minister at Manakin Church n.d. (Box 17)
- Railway line n.d. (Box 17)
- Agreement- Harry Heth and French n.d. (Box 17)
- List of property owned by Scot n.d. (Box 17)
- Directions concerning medicine n.d. (Box 17)
- List of furniture n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Joseph Tidball to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from H. W. Kenna to William F. Carter n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from C. O. Hand to Henry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from E. H. Randolph to [?] [?] May 31 (Box 17)
- Comments on the Trojan War n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from N. G. to Lavinia Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from Ann F. Randolph to Lavinia Randolph [?] Feb 21 (Box 17)
- Letter from James F. Leitch to Harry Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Poem by Lavinia R. Randolph n.d. (Box 17)
- Letter from A. H. to John Heth n.d. (Box 17)
- Map by Joseph Watkins n.d. (Box 17)
- Unidentified letters (7) n.d. (Box 17)